<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Triet Vo&#39;s new cool site</title>
        <link>https://trietmvo.com/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Triet Vo&#39;s new cool site</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>triet.vo@nyu.edu (Triet Vo)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>triet.vo@nyu.edu (Triet Vo)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 20:02:24 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://trietmvo.com/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Meeting Wifey!~~</title>
    <link>https://trietmvo.com/posts/meeting-wifey/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 20:02:24 -0700</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://trietmvo.com/posts/meeting-wifey/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[ ]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Luna, stablecoin and WAGMI</title>
    <link>https://trietmvo.com/posts/stablecoin/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:28:13 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://trietmvo.com/posts/stablecoin/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[For those who aren&rsquo;t familiar with blockchain (which, lucky you&hellip;), there&rsquo;s a cryptocurrency called Luna/UST that crashes. Not just any random coin btw, it&rsquo;s on the top 5/10 of cryptocurrencies. It&rsquo;s actually used as a stablecoin (algorithmic stablecoin, to be exact&hellip;) which is just a fancy term for an alternative to a dollar. It tries to artificially cap the price to be exactly 1 dollar, and if you think suppressing something&rsquo;s price is a bad idea, well you&rsquo;re correct.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Some fun technique I found while doing competitive programming puzzles: Regex DP</title>
    <link>https://trietmvo.com/posts/regex-dp/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:28:13 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://trietmvo.com/posts/regex-dp/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I do some competitive programming problems for fun, because I have a twisted sense of humor. Recently, I repeatedly encounter a pattern in those problems with a very elegant dynamic programming solution. I haven&rsquo;t seen anything like this elsewhere, although I&rsquo;m somewhat aware that regex do use DP. The pattern I&rsquo;m noticing is more of regex + subsequence. Let&rsquo;s give a concrete example:
Given a sequence of 0 and 1. Supposed that you can choose any [l,r] interval and reverse them (only once).]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Wave added!</title>
    <link>https://trietmvo.com/posts/wave/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 19:47:38 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://trietmvo.com/posts/wave/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I created a way to wave using Ethereum wallet!
This is mostly thanks to buildspace and Farza, a great blockchain instructor that taught the Solidity course. I was just followed along =)
They have a Twitch stream every few days or so. Basically lecture. Feel free to explore if you want.
I&rsquo;ll probably add a log and some other forms to wave soon, for people who just wanna leave a message or so.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>First Guitar Arrangement!</title>
    <link>https://trietmvo.com/posts/first-guitar-arrangement/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 16:30:35 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://trietmvo.com/posts/first-guitar-arrangement/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I arranged my first ever guitar song!
It&rsquo;s for this song. From an anime ofc. Very good anime at that; don&rsquo;t be fooled by the title, it&rsquo;s not about that.
I&rsquo;ll upload both the Guitar Pro and PDF in due time to the Google Drive folder. Frankly, I&rsquo;m too lazy to do it rn so&hellip; But I&rsquo;ll leave it free as a contribution to the guitar community that I constantly pulled tabs from.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Guitar Update 2</title>
    <link>https://trietmvo.com/posts/guitar_update_2/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 16:30:35 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://trietmvo.com/posts/guitar_update_2/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Any anime guitar repo would be incomplete without K-On, literally the greatest guitar anime there ever was. Therefore, the Drive folder now includes K-On.
Also, my guitar repos are all tabs available online, and they are made available by very good and generous people (who are much more talented than me) that made these tabs and distribute it for free (some example: vvxo, Aethersan , Tam Lu, okayan_zeak21, and Very Nize).]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>The Obsession with Sports</title>
    <link>https://trietmvo.com/posts/sport/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 23:25:38 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://trietmvo.com/posts/sport/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[It&rsquo;s the NBA finals, and this reminds me that it&rsquo;s time for shitpost. I haven&rsquo;t shitpost enough about anime, so time to talk about sports. I&rsquo;m not qualified to talk about professional sports like your usual ESPN analysts (not that they&rsquo;re even qualified to begin with), so I won&rsquo;t. However, I did play a couple of sports: Tennis tournament when I was young, swimming, soccer (cuz I&rsquo;m Asian), and basketball in high school (I still cross people up).]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Big brain stuff I found on Codeforces</title>
    <link>https://trietmvo.com/posts/cf_2/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 22:27:44 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://trietmvo.com/posts/cf_2/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[There are a lot of big brain solutions on Codeforces. Or maybe I&rsquo;m just too small-brained or haven&rsquo;t learned these things yet.
This was the problem I found today.
As usual, I have no idea how to do this shit (within the time limit). I thought about DP, but then I saw the n &lt;= 10^9. Any dp solution will probably requires at least N^2 - you&rsquo;ll have to loop from 1 to 10^9, and then you have to find divisors of all number.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Dumb it down: Edmond-Karps, Max-Flow-Min-Cut, Support Vector Machine, VPC/Networking</title>
    <link>https://trietmvo.com/posts/explanation_1/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 04:21:20 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://trietmvo.com/posts/explanation_1/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Besides sleeping and watching anime, I also do some studying too (emphasized on some). Sometimes, I read on topics from Algorithm/Competitive Programming, continuing my Coursera course on ML , or continue to blow shit up in AWS just because. I also forget stuff pretty quickly, so I&rsquo;ll try to document what I learned today here. Also try to see how deep I really understand what I read because if you can&rsquo;t understand what I&rsquo;m talking about here (even if you aren&rsquo;t a CS major), then there&rsquo;s a high chance I just don&rsquo;t know what I&rsquo;m talking about.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Chess going mainstream, and how to have fun playing chess</title>
    <link>https://trietmvo.com/posts/chess_joy/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 22:17:33 -0500</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://trietmvo.com/posts/chess_joy/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I played chess. A bit. Since 5th grade or so.
I won some tournament back in Vietnam and here in US (not scholastic lmao). Some of my games under USCF are online, however most of the game I played in Vietnam (when I was stupid and sacked all my pieces) are lost. I kept annotation of all games, but I threw away most of it when I went to the US.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
